<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>urbandead on Arcane Endpoint</title>
    <link>http://archmage.me/tags/urbandead/</link>
    <description>Recent content in urbandead on Arcane Endpoint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 10:31:38 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://archmage.me/tags/urbandead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Urban Burial</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/urban-burial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 10:31:38 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/urban-burial/</guid>
      <description>Hello, readers. Today, for you, I have some sad news.
Effective immediately, I&amp;rsquo;m announcing an indefinite suspension of my contributions to Urban Dead and its community. This decision has not been made lightly, and warrants an elaboration, so as to dissuade further harm from being done.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been an active participant in the community for about six months, after a long hiatus. In this time I&amp;rsquo;ve created three new characters, joined several groups, spent a lot of time around other players, and even worked on a custom desktop client for the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain-Culling - &#34;Horde Eviction Done Right&#34;</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/chain-culling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/chain-culling/</guid>
      <description>Hello, everyone! It&amp;rsquo;s Kara here, and I&amp;rsquo;ve got some wisdom to share! Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to be talking about a new strategy I discovered, for coordinating zombie eviction efforts. I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;ll be of use to plenty of the folks in Malton, so be sure to share the info around with your friends! After all, folks that survive together thrive together!
-Kara Valentine
Overview The basic idea behind chain-culling is to effectively combat large hordes camping in a single building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malton Happenings, November 2018</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-2018-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-2018-11/</guid>
      <description>THE VALENTINE SISTERS have been surviving as usual, though this month has been a bit harder than usual on the sisters. A number of peculiar happenings occured, too.
ASTRA and THE LOCKETTSIDE VALKYRIES vailantly defended their home base, St Alexander&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Lockettside, from the vile and coordinated attacks of THE DEAD, but after days of overwhelming pressure, both St Alexander&amp;rsquo;s and the adjacent Tompson Mall were broken into and ransacked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malton Happenings, October 2018</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-oct-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-oct-2018/</guid>
      <description>After a couple of months in the deadly streets of Malton, THE VALENTINE SISTERS have settled in, and managed to survive through their compassion, skills and resourcefulness.
  The sisters and their operation areas.
  ASTRA spent several weeks around YAGOTON, and found the area to be too quiet for her tastes. Stocking up on medkits and tending to the few injured survivors she came across, she struggled to utilise her skills to the fullest&amp;hellip; until a phone call from NAOMI brought news!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>