<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on Arcane Endpoint</title>
    <link>http://archmage.me/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on Arcane Endpoint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:29:23 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://archmage.me/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/vulnerability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:29:23 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/vulnerability/</guid>
      <description>A quick update this time. I was doing well, and now I&amp;rsquo;m not. Between last time and now, I quit my job, went to Chicago for a month, met my long-distance girlfriend, came home and started a new job.
I&amp;rsquo;m really sad and lonely. I&amp;rsquo;ve felt myself retreating from the world in my usual ways, only this time it&amp;rsquo;s been a lot more consistent. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken steps back from friends that have been around for years, in some cases for perfectly justified reasons, and yet, endlessly subtracting just leaves you with nothing at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope Found</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/hope-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 09:16:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/hope-found/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been up in Sydney for the Easter weekend, spending time with family and friends. Throughout all of this, it&amp;rsquo;s been evident that I&amp;rsquo;ve regressed a lot since moving to Melbourne and being immersed in the struggle of existence under capitalism.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a root cause of my deterioration for a long time, but after a really helpful conversation with my girlfriend, Bri, I think I&amp;rsquo;ve finally found a way forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message Received</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/message-received/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 18:56:41 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/message-received/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been battling a lot lately. Battling is really the only way I can describe it.
Work&amp;rsquo;s been hellish and cruel. Life&amp;rsquo;s been hellish and cruel. I&amp;rsquo;m really, really struggling.
Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been dwelling a lot on the notion (and manifestations) of rejection. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty simple - people see someone or something that they don&amp;rsquo;t like, and they reject it. Rejection comes in a lot of forms, from overt to covert, but it&amp;rsquo;s always the same sentiment: &amp;ldquo;I do not want this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>