<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Arcane Endpoint</title>
    <link>http://archmage.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Arcane Endpoint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:29:23 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://archmage.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/vulnerability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:29:23 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/vulnerability/</guid>
      <description>A quick update this time. I was doing well, and now I&amp;rsquo;m not. Between last time and now, I quit my job, went to Chicago for a month, met my long-distance girlfriend, came home and started a new job.
I&amp;rsquo;m really sad and lonely. I&amp;rsquo;ve felt myself retreating from the world in my usual ways, only this time it&amp;rsquo;s been a lot more consistent. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken steps back from friends that have been around for years, in some cases for perfectly justified reasons, and yet, endlessly subtracting just leaves you with nothing at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urban Burial</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/urban-burial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 10:31:38 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/urban-burial/</guid>
      <description>Hello, readers. Today, for you, I have some sad news.
Effective immediately, I&amp;rsquo;m announcing an indefinite suspension of my contributions to Urban Dead and its community. This decision has not been made lightly, and warrants an elaboration, so as to dissuade further harm from being done.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been an active participant in the community for about six months, after a long hiatus. In this time I&amp;rsquo;ve created three new characters, joined several groups, spent a lot of time around other players, and even worked on a custom desktop client for the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope Found</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/hope-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 09:16:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/hope-found/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been up in Sydney for the Easter weekend, spending time with family and friends. Throughout all of this, it&amp;rsquo;s been evident that I&amp;rsquo;ve regressed a lot since moving to Melbourne and being immersed in the struggle of existence under capitalism.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a root cause of my deterioration for a long time, but after a really helpful conversation with my girlfriend, Bri, I think I&amp;rsquo;ve finally found a way forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message Received</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/message-received/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 18:56:41 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/message-received/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been battling a lot lately. Battling is really the only way I can describe it.
Work&amp;rsquo;s been hellish and cruel. Life&amp;rsquo;s been hellish and cruel. I&amp;rsquo;m really, really struggling.
Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been dwelling a lot on the notion (and manifestations) of rejection. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty simple - people see someone or something that they don&amp;rsquo;t like, and they reject it. Rejection comes in a lot of forms, from overt to covert, but it&amp;rsquo;s always the same sentiment: &amp;ldquo;I do not want this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Void State</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/void-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 00:29:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/void-state/</guid>
      <description>Hey. Today I&amp;rsquo;m gonna write about me, like last post. Unlike last post, things aren&amp;rsquo;t great right now. It&amp;rsquo;s 12:30am the night of a work day, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to write a bunch, push this to the repo then go the fuck to sleep.
Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing pretty badly. My mental state is shot. A combination of three factors has led to this state:
 I met an online friend in meatspace, which was confronting for unrelated reasons I broke off contact with a person who has treated me poorly for a few months I started working for a client in a capacity that is extremely draining  I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about each of these individually, since that seems like a good way of healing what damage has been done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain-Culling - &#34;Horde Eviction Done Right&#34;</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/chain-culling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/chain-culling/</guid>
      <description>Hello, everyone! It&amp;rsquo;s Kara here, and I&amp;rsquo;ve got some wisdom to share! Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to be talking about a new strategy I discovered, for coordinating zombie eviction efforts. I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;ll be of use to plenty of the folks in Malton, so be sure to share the info around with your friends! After all, folks that survive together thrive together!
-Kara Valentine
Overview The basic idea behind chain-culling is to effectively combat large hordes camping in a single building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malton Happenings, November 2018</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-2018-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-2018-11/</guid>
      <description>THE VALENTINE SISTERS have been surviving as usual, though this month has been a bit harder than usual on the sisters. A number of peculiar happenings occured, too.
ASTRA and THE LOCKETTSIDE VALKYRIES vailantly defended their home base, St Alexander&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Lockettside, from the vile and coordinated attacks of THE DEAD, but after days of overwhelming pressure, both St Alexander&amp;rsquo;s and the adjacent Tompson Mall were broken into and ransacked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for Netrunner Nationals Tournament Australia 2018</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/preparing-for-netrunner-nationals-tournament-australia-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 14:24:32 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/preparing-for-netrunner-nationals-tournament-australia-2018/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a very exciting time for Australian Netrunner players this week - the Netrunner Nationals tournament for 2018 in Australia is on this weekend in Melbourne!
Around this time, folks are flying in from all corners of the country to participate in what will be the last ever official Australian Nationals tournament, scheduled on Saturday, 13 October.
There are two factors of note that should make this a particularly interesting tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malton Happenings, October 2018</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-oct-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-oct-2018/</guid>
      <description>After a couple of months in the deadly streets of Malton, THE VALENTINE SISTERS have settled in, and managed to survive through their compassion, skills and resourcefulness.
  The sisters and their operation areas.
  ASTRA spent several weeks around YAGOTON, and found the area to be too quiet for her tastes. Stocking up on medkits and tending to the few injured survivors she came across, she struggled to utilise her skills to the fullest&amp;hellip; until a phone call from NAOMI brought news!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Valentine Sisters</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/valentine-sisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/valentine-sisters/</guid>
      <description>In MALTON, the city of endless hunger, war rages between the living and the dead. Safety is scarce, danger is abundant, and the comforts of civilisation are few and far between. Survivors stave off death by any means, while the dead surge across the suburbs in great hordes, sowing great chaos and destruction.
THE VALENTINE SISTERS are a trio of talented, passionate and persistent survivors who reside in Malton. Doomed by a terrible curse that activates if they are ever near another sister, they live out separate lives in different suburbs, though each is only a phonecall away.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>