<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>archmage on Arcane Endpoint</title>
    <link>http://archmage.me/author/archmage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in archmage on Arcane Endpoint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://archmage.me/author/archmage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain-Culling - &#34;Horde Eviction Done Right&#34;</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/chain-culling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/chain-culling/</guid>
      <description>Hello, everyone! It&amp;rsquo;s Kara Valentine here, and I&amp;rsquo;ve got some wisdom to share! Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to be talking about a new strategy I discovered, for coordinating zombie eviction efforts. I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;ll be of use to plenty of the folks in Malton, so be sure to share the info around with your friends! After all, folks that survive together thrive together!
-Kara Valentine
Overview The basic idea behind chain-culling is to effectively combat large hordes camping in a single building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malton Happenings, November 2018</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-2018-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-2018-11/</guid>
      <description>THE VALENTINE SISTERS have been surviving as usual, though this month has been a bit harder than usual on the sisters. A number of peculiar happenings occured, too.
ASTRA and THE LOCKETTSIDE VALKYRIES vailantly defended their home base, St Alexander&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Lockettside, from the vile and coordinated attacks of THE DEAD, but after days of overwhelming pressure, both St Alexander&amp;rsquo;s and the adjacent Tompson Mall were broken into and ransacked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for Netrunner Nationals Tournament Australia 2018</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/preparing-for-netrunner-nationals-tournament-australia-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 14:24:32 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/preparing-for-netrunner-nationals-tournament-australia-2018/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a very exciting time for Australian Netrunner players this week - the Netrunner Nationals tournament for 2018 in Australia is on this weekend in Melbourne!
Around this time, folks are flying in from all corners of the country to participate in what will be the last ever official Australian Nationals tournament, scheduled on Saturday, 13 October.
There are two factors of note that should make this a particularly interesting tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malton Happenings, October 2018</title>
      <link>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-oct-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://archmage.me/posts/malton-happenings-oct-2018/</guid>
      <description>After a couple of months in the deadly streets of Malton, THE VALENTINE SISTERS have settled in, and managed to survive through their compassion, skills and resourcefulness.
   The sisters and their operation areas.   ASTRA spent several weeks around YAGOTON, and found the area to be too quiet for her tastes. Stocking up on medkits and tending to the few injured survivors she came across, she struggled to utilise her skills to the fullest&amp;hellip; until a phone call from NAOMI brought news!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>